24小时
第三季  第11集
前情提要
你很了解我 所以不要对我做的事感到惊讶
You know me well enough not to be surprised if there are repercussions.
我希望你不是在威胁我
I hope you're not threatening me.
我没有威胁你 大卫 只是实话实说
I don't make threats, David. Just tell it like it is.
他在威胁你 他可以帮你开始你的政治生涯
What he's doing is showing you that not only did he have the power to help start your political career
但也可以终结它
but he also has the power to put an end to it.
必须要找到他
There has to be a way to get to him.
大卫? 怎么了?
David? What... What's wrong?
我需要你的帮忙
I need your help.
赫克托 和 拉姆 正试图买一种病毒当做武器
Hector and Ramon are trying to buy a virus to use as a weapon.
成百万的人可能会死去
Millions of people could die.
我策划了这次交易 这样政府就能掌控并摧毁这些病毒
I set up this deal so my government could take control of the virus and destroy it.
你还在为反恐局工作?
You're still with CTU?
是的
Yes, I'm still with CTU.
我不能让病毒落入坏人手中
I cannot allow this virus to get into the wrong hands.
我从杰克那得知 他们要买的病毒
I have a message from Jack. The virus that they are going to buy
杰克要从他们手中夺过来
Jack is going to take it from them.
杰克答应如果我帮你 就把我和我家人弄出去
Jack promised to get me and my family out of here if I help you.
快点! 快点!
Hurry! Hurry!
鲍尔和萨拉扎兄弟在墨西哥
Bauer was with the Salazar brothers in Mexico.
他的应答器没信号
His transponder signal stopped working.
我们将尽力和他取得联系
We're doing everything we can to re-establish contact.
通知特种部队 没我命令不要行动
Tell the delta units to hold their position till I get back to you.
事情变复杂了 有其他买家对病毒有兴趣
There's been a complication. Another buyer's interested in the virus.
你在说什么? 我们说好的
What are you talking about? We have a deal.
我们将拍卖 病毒卖给出价最高的人
We'll hold an auction and the virus will go to the highest bidder.
我们刚发现 还有一人参与了交易
We just found out there's another player in the deal.
-是谁?  -尼娜·迈尔斯
-Who is it?  -Nina Meyers.
你们的出价是两亿二千五百万美元
Your bid is 225 million dollars.
她的是两亿四千万美元 她赢了
And hers is 240. You win.
-我们可以得到病毒  -怎么得到?
-We can get the virus.  -How do you get the virus?
我告诉过你 我认识她! 我可以找她!
I told you. I know her! I can get to her!
萨拉扎兄弟愿意付你十倍薪酬
The Salazars are willing to pay you at least 10 times more than what you're getting paid right now.
你会原谅我杀了你的妻子吗?
Are you gonna be able to forgive me for killing your wife?
如果我要报复 尼娜 我早可杀了你
If I wanted revenge, Nina, I would have killed you already.
我只想结束这个交易 然后永远消失
All I wanna do is finish this deal and disappear for good.
证明给我看
Convince me.
以下事件发生于晚上11点至凌晨12点之间
The following takes place between 11:00 pm and 12:00 am.
-亚当 阿马多尔行动了吗?  -没有 他被困在那了
-Adam, is Amador moving yet?  -No, he's still stopped at the location.
-那地区情况怎么样?  -主要是郊区 建筑很少
-What do we know about the area?  -Hmm, it's mostly rural, there's very few structures.
-有红外线吗?  -有
-Do we have infrared on it?  -Yeah.
但不是高解像度卫星
It's not high res satellite but there appear
不过可以看出附近有车和人
to be a number of vehicles and bodies nearby
不知道是谁?
but we have no idea what they are.
给他点空间 让他感到去送病毒很安全
All right. Give him space. We wanna make sure he feels safe enough to take delivery of the virus.
明白
Got it.
蔡斯·埃德蒙兹怎么样了?
What's the latest on Chase Edmunds?
他从赫克托那逃走后 告诉了特种部队他的位置
After he escaped from Hector he phoned his position in to delta teams
现在他们正找他
and they're on their way to pick him up now.
埃德蒙兹! 你情况如何?
Edmunds, stop! Commander Reese. What's your condition?
手中枪了 但没事
Shot in the hand but I'm fine.
其他人呢?
What about the others?
有两个人和我在一起
I've got two people. They're coming with me.
我们发现了一辆车 正向这边驶来
We've spotted a vehicle from the air, heading this way.
是萨拉扎兄弟 不能让他们知道反恐局在这 赶快离开!
It's the Salazars. They can't know that CTU is down here. We need to leave now!
恩 我们走
Then let's get them out of here.
塞尔吉奥! 上飞机 我们去一个安全的的地方
Sergio! Get on the chopper. We're going to a safe place, all right? We're going to go right now.
我不能就这样丢下她
I can't leave her like this.
赫克托来了 你要为儿子考虑
Hector's coming. You need to think about your son.
我们走
We go. Follow us.
走! 我们走! 快! 快!
We gotta go, now! Let's go, let's go! Move, move, move!
弯腰走! 快点! 弯腰!
Keep them low, keep them low! Get them in there, come on! Stay low, stay low!
-喂?  -艾伦? 我是韦恩·帕默尔
-Yes?  -Allan? It's Wayne Palmer.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我想你除了通过我哥威胁我之外 手中还有别的牌
You know, I always thought you had more balls than to trick me through my brother.
你不能像个男人那样和我谈判吗?
What? You can't talk to me, man on man?
我无须向你解释 你睡了我老婆!
I don't owe you an explanation. You slept with my wife!
这是我和你的事 艾伦
That's between you and me, Allan.
没问题! 你下台就一笔勾销了
Fine! Step down. And it all goes away.
你在痴人说梦话
That's not your decision.
走着瞧
We'll see.
韦恩.
Wayne
你在和谁说话?
Who are you talking to?
艾伦·米利肯.
Allan Milliken
-你知道自己在做什么吗?  -收拾自己的乱局
-What the hell do you think you're doing?  -Cleaning up my own mess, David.
-艾伦!  -总统先生!
-Hello, Allan!  -Mr President!
你的兄弟就要成为你的灾难了
That brother of yours is going to be your undoing.
-我不会炒掉他  -那太糟了
-I'm not firing my brother.  -That's too bad.
我不会放弃卫生保健法案 我花了两年的时间完成它
And I have no intention of losing my Health Care bill. I spent two years putting it together.
但是你还差三票 我调查过了
Except you're three votes short, last I checked.
好好享受失望的滋味吧
You'd better brace yourself for some disappointment.
我不想和你开战 艾伦
I don't want to go to war with you, Allan.
-你选择的 总统先生  -你给的条件无法接受
-It's your choice, Mr President.  -The choice you're giving me is unacceptable.
总会有别的办法
There has to be another way to work this out.
在其他问题上我可以让步
On any other issue I'd bend over backwards to accomodate you.
这个不行
Not on this one.
那你将为你的所作所为负责
Then you'll have only yourself to blame for the consequences.
我向你保证
And I promise you...
一定不会让你好受
You won't like them.
雪莉什么时候来?
When is Sherry getting here?
五分钟之内
In five minutes.
大卫 你确定要把她卷入此事?
David, are you sure you want to bring her into this?
我们跟人家干上了 韦恩 她可以帮很大忙
We're gonna street fight, Wayne. That's what she does best.
我俩必须集中精力 关注墨西哥的事态发展
And we both have to focus on what's happening in Mexico.
我们都希望胜利 但也要做好失败的准备
I know we're hoping for success but we have to anticipate failure.
如果杰克·鲍尔没能截获病毒
If Jack Bauer does not intercept the virus
那我们就要对付一场国际危难
then we are dealing with an international crisis.
这是迈克尔 阿马多尔 他代表乌克兰进行病毒交易
This is Michael Amador. He's representing the Ukrainians in the sale of the virus.
特种部队在秘密跟踪他
Now, we have a delta team tracking him on the ground, at a safe distance.
为何不现在就抓他?
Why don't they just get Amador now if they know where he is?
因为他身上可能没有带着病毒
Cause he may not be carrying the virus.
如果这样 我们就前功尽弃了
And if he's not we'll have blown our chance at the interception.
一旦杰克确认是病毒 特种部队会立即采取行动
Once Jack confirms it is the virus then the delta teams will go in and secure it.
特种部队要一张和杰克一起的那女人的照片
Delta asked for a photo of the woman Jack's working with.
-我发过去...  -亚当 等等
-So, I sent them this...  -Adam, wait.
尼娜·迈尔斯是经纪人?
Nina Meyers is the broker?
你不知道吗?
Didn't you read the ops brief?
不知道
No.
金 跟我来
Kim, come with me.
-麻烦你开完简报会  -好的
-Can you finish the briefing, please  -Yeah.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-我在寻找合适的时机告诉你  -我不敢相信尼娜·迈尔斯也介入了此事
-I was looking for the right time to tell you.  -I cannot believe Nina Meyers is involved in this.
你父亲需要她帮忙 才能保证病毒安全
Your father needed her help to secure the virus.
她杀了我妈妈
She killed my mother.
我父亲甚至不能假装跟她合作
My father couldn't even pretend to work with her.
抱歉 杰克
I'm sorry, Jack.
抱歉
Sorry, Jack.
我试着认为你已经改变了 但我能感觉到
I wanted to think you'd changed but I can feel it.
你在说谎
You're lying.
你什么事情也没忘掉 是吗?
You haven't forgotten anything, have you?
你看不起我
You despise me.
你现在所做的一切只是让我帮你完成计划
And you'd do anything right now to get me to go along with your plan.
-不是的  -就是
-It's not true.  -It is true.
我知道你还在反恐局工作
I know you're still with CTU.
那我为何还要让你摆布我?
So, why would I let you set me up?
你爱怎么想 随便你
Now. You can believe whatever you want.
我必须让这笔生意成交 我是个逃犯 我别无选择
But I need this deal to happen. I'm a fugitive, I don't have a choice.
我要萨拉扎兄弟支付病毒的钱
I need the Salazars to pay me for the virus and right now,
而阿马多尔只和你交易
you're the only person Amador will deal with.
你明白吗?
Do you understand me?
我会按原来的标准给你两千万美元
I'll honor your original deal. You'll get your 20 million dollars.
-而且你可以保住性命  -直到他们没有收到买的东西
-And you get to keep breating.  -Until my client doesn't get what he paid for.
现在
Right now,
你不必担心你的委托人
your client should be the least of your worries.
赫克托!
Hector!
她死了
She's dead.
走开!
Get out from that!
克劳迪娅!
Claudia!
他们不可能走太远 快去找
They can't be far away. Find them.
快去找! 快去!
Find them! Find them!
墨西哥当局因我们没有及早通知他们而大发雷霆
I just spoke to the Mexican authorities and they're pissed off that we didn't notify them earlier.
是赫克托
It's Hector.
准备好了?
You set?
开始!
Go!
-喂  -是我
-Yeah.  -It's me.
埃德蒙兹逃掉了 他杀了我三个人
Edmunds escaped. He killed three of my men.
他有没有联系反恐局?
Has he contacted CTU?
还没有 他可能不会打来了
Not yet. But he may not call.
埃德蒙兹是个混混 他是在单独行动
We found out Edmunds is a rogue. He's been acting on his own.
反恐局没有派人到这里来找他吗?
Then CTU hasn't sent anyone out here to find him?
他们甚至不知道他在哪里
They don't even know where he is.
-有他消息立即通知我  -好的
-Ok, you call me the second you hear from him.  -Yeah.
-喂?  -你还和鲍尔在一起吗?
-Yeah?  -Are you still with Bauer?
我在进城的主道上 等鲍尔带那个女人来
I'm at the main road that leads into town, waiting for Bauer to bring the woman.
拉姆 我们必须取消交易
Ramon, we have to call this off.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
-那个反恐局探员 他逃掉了  -怎么会?
-The CTU agent, Edmunds. He escaped.  -How?
我... 我不知道 克劳迪娅和他一起
I... I don't know. Claudia was with him.
拉姆 她死了
Ramon. She's dead.
我很难过 但我们还有生意要做
I'm sorry. But Hector, you still have business to do.
不能让埃德蒙兹活着 他一找到电话就会联系反恐局
Not with that much of a use. As soon as he gets to a phone he'll call CTU.
在那之前找到他
Find him before that happens.
我正在找 但天太黑了 不可能找到他
I'm trying but it's too dark. He'll be impossible to track.
你有什么建议?
What are you suggesting we do?
取消这次交易 太危险了!
Forget this whole thing, it's too dangerous!
-做事当然有危险  -但不像现在这样!
-It's always been dangerous.  -Not like this!
听我说 你是促成这笔交易的关键人物
Hey, listen to me. You are the one who made this deal.
你向买家做出了保证
You promised our buyer something we can't deliver.
如果你不信守诺言 我的名声和所有的努力
If you don't keep your promise, my reputation and everything I worked for
就毁了 你明白吗?
will be ruined. Do you understand?
我明白
I understand.
让你一些手下找埃德蒙兹 其余的都带过来 准备交易
Keep some of your men looking for Edmunds and bring the rest of the men here so we can do the deal.
喂
Yes.
-拉姆 我是杰克 事情都准备好了吗?  -恩
-Ramon, it's Jack. Everything clear outside?  -Yes.
我要你回到这儿来
Ok, I need you to come back to the building.
那个女人同意和我们合作吗?
Did the woman agree to work with us?
你过来我再和你解释
I'll explain when you get here.
进来
Yeah.
-总统先生?  -什么事 埃里克?
-Mr President?  -Yes, Eric?
雪莉 帕默尔来了
Sherry Palmer's here.
让她进来
Show her in.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好 雪莉
Hello, Sherry.
大卫
David.
谢谢你 埃里克
Thank you, Eric.
-请坐  -不 谢谢 我
-Please, have a seat.  -No, thank you, I, er
我还是站着吧
I'd rather stand.
安妮现在还好吧?
So... How are things with Anne?
-很好  -那就好
-They're fine.  -Good.
我很高兴 你应该感到高兴
I'm glad. You, er, you deserve a little bit of happiness.
谢谢
Thank you.
你气色不错 但有点变了
You're looking well. But somehow different.
-变老了点?  -不是
-A little older?  -No, it's not that.
你看起来很平静
You look calm.
呃 可能是累了 但我不知道怎么会平静
Erm, tired maybe, but, er, I'm not sure exactly how calm.
我知道过去三年 你过的很艰苦
I know these last three years have been difficult.
没有想的那样辛苦
Well, erm, not as difficult as they could have been.
我该为此感谢你
And I have you to thank for that.
你让我不用坐牢 免受公众侮辱
Kept me out of prison, away from public humiliation.
我 呃 我失去了很多
I, erm, I lost a lot.
但我发现很多事情 原本就不是那么重要
But most of it, I discovered, really wasn't that important to begin with.
这让我吃惊 想象一下!
Which surprised me. Imagine that!
什么? 什么那么好笑?
What? What's... What's funny?
不 没什么 真的
No, nothing really.
我曾经摆脱你 因为你狠得像鲨鱼
It's just that, when I wanted you to fall back, and just let things be, you were a shark.
现在我请你回来 要你再做回鲨鱼
Now that I've asked you back, and need you to be a shark...
你要我做什么 我就还能做什么
I can still be whatever you need me to be.
谢谢
Thank you.
你说你和米利肯之间有麻烦?
So you say you're having some kind of trouble with Milliken?
是的
Yes. I am.
说说吧
Ok. Tell me all about it.
手铐? 我以为你能博取她的信任
Handcuffs? I thought you were going to gain her trust.
我会的 只是要比我希望的时间要长
I will. It's just going to take a little longer than I hoped.
她同意去做交易 这才是关键
She agreed to do the exchange, that's what's important.
什么时候?
When is it happening?
-阿马多尔打电话来就行动  -阿马多尔 最好快点打来 我们时间不多了
-As soon as Amador calls.  -Amador had better call soon. We might not have much time.
你同伙逃走了
Your partner has escaped.
你本该让我杀了他
You should have let me kill him when I had the chance.
是的
Yes, I should have.
不知道什么原因克劳迪娅和他在一起 她死了
For some reason Claudia was with him. She ended up dead.
你在说什么? 怎么会?
What are you talking about? How?
赫克托没有说
Hector didn't say.
告诉赫克托我很抱歉
Tell Hector I'm sorry.
他来的时候你自己告诉他
Tell him yourself when he gets here.
尼娜 我需要你打开这份交易文档 阿马多尔要验证你客户的资金
Nina, I need you to open up this transaction file. Amador is gonna want to verify your client's funds.
快!
Now!
艾伦就是想看到韦恩下台
Bottom line is, Allan's determined to see Wayne removed.
即使这意味着对我总统任期的毁灭
Even if it means destroying my presidency.
-你想和平地解决这个问题?  -当然
-And you've tried to work this out peacefully?  -Of course.
艾伦是不会让步的 在他眼里 这是尊严问题
Allan wouldn't budge. In Allan's mind, it's a matter of pride.
所以你想让我找到一些 可以用来对付艾伦的东西?
So, you want me to find something you can use against Allan?
我知道你了解艾伦的事情
I've always known that you knew things about Allan
碍于我和他的交情而没有告诉我
that you didn't tell me because of my frienship with him.
我也知道你很聪明不会去问
And I've always known you were too smart to ask.
我想我们都是对的
I guess we were both right.
阿伦是有不可告人的事 他会为此付出一切代价
Allan does have skeletons in his closet that he would gard at any cost.
我要提醒你 大卫
One particular comes to mind. But I must warn you, David.
这是件大事
It's a big one.
-是什么?  -你要知道如果你打出这张牌
-What is it?  -All you need to know is that if you play this card,
你和艾伦·米利肯下半辈子都会是敌人
you and Allan Milliken will be enemies for the rest of your life.
在我看来 我们的友谊在他勒索我时就已经结束了
As far as I'm concerned, our friendship ended when he tried to extort me.
我可以帮你
Then I can help you.
克劳迪娅死了 她为什么会死?
Claudia is dead. Why did she die?
为了我们的安全 你姐姐很勇敢 塞尔吉奥
So we could be safe. Your sister was very brave, Sergio.
我们再也不用惧怕赫克托了
Now we don't have to worry about Hector no more.
可我喜欢赫克托
But I like Hector.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
是 长官 明白 收到
Yes, sir, will do. Copy that.
-行了 给我吧  -还没完成呢
-That's good enough, give it to me.  -But, I'm not finished.
Reese 出什么事了?
Reese, what's going on?
赫克托 萨拉扎在找你 反恐局要我撤回监视队
Hector Salazar's looking for you. CTU wants me to fall back my surveillance team.
等等 我们不能跟丢阿马多尔!
Wait a minute, we can't lose Amador!
不会的 反恐局正在通过电话跟踪他
We won't. CTU's tracking him through his cell phone.
他可以丢掉电话 我们需要看到他
Well he can dump his cell phone. We need visual.
别担心 这已经不是你管的了
Don't worry about that. It's not your problem anymore.
别说不管我的事! 过去一年都是我负责的!
Don't tell me it's not my problem! It's been my problem for the last year!
听着 埃德蒙兹 你需要治疗
Look, Edmunds. You need medical attention.
我们要带你撤离 还有小孩和他父亲
We're evacuating you with the boy and his father now.
我哪里也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
-卡佩勒先生!  -什么事
-Mr. Chapelle!  -Yeah.
检测到在阿马多尔位置有热影像在移动
I'm picking up on some heat signatures moving in on Amador's position.
-地面车辆?  -从速度看来应该是
-Ground vehicles?  -From the speed, it looks like it.
车上可能有病毒
All right. This may be the virus.
我该干什么? 联系特种部队吗?
What protocoles do you want me on? You want me to contact the delta teams?
恩 让他们警戒 但在阿马多尔和鲍尔碰面前别让他们靠近
Yeah. Put them on alert but make sure they don't approach until Amador meets bauer.
要看到病毒
We want a visual on the virus.
好的 明白
Ok, got it.
-雪莉  -韦恩!
-Sherry.  -Wayne!
你来这里干什么?
What are you doing in here?
我在等他们为我准备办公室
Oh, I'm just waiting for them to prepare an office for me.
见到你很高兴 雪莉 但老实说
It's good to see you Sherry, but, to be blunt,
我认为你在这里 不是个好主意
I don't think your being here is such a good idea.
你当然不会赞同
Well, of course you don't, sweetie.
整件事情都是因为你和朱莉娅的苟且之事
That's because this whole thing is about your indiscretion with Julia.
-雪莉!  -我并没有指责你的意思
-Oh, Sherry!  -I say that with no judgement.
当然 你哪有资格指责别人
Of course you do since you're the last person on earth who's in a position to pass judgement.
好了 韦恩 我们别说这个了
Ok, Wayne, let's not play this. We're both too good at it.
你想说什么?
So, what do you want me to hear?
我很感激你回来帮大卫
Listen, I do appreciate you coming down here to help David...
不 直接说正题
No-no-no-no-no, skip that part.
好吧 我忘了你的个性
That's right, I forgot that about you.
听我说 雪莉 你在这里爱干什么就干什么
Listen, Sherry, do whatever it is that you do around here for a few hours.
但我希望你告诉大卫你找不到
But then I want you to tell David that you were unable to find out
对付艾伦·米利肯的办法
anything that he could use on Allan Milliken.
如果我找不到 你就得出局?
So, you know if I do that, the only way out of this is if you resign?
这正是我想要的
Just what I wanna do.
大卫不想那样
Well, David doesn't want that.
坦白的说 我也不想
And frankly, neither do I.
雪莉 你为什么要操心?
Sherry, why do you care?
因为大卫需要像我这样的人
Because David needs someone like me.
可以正确看待事物的人
Someone who sees things the way they really are.
并且随时可以反击的人
Who's not afraid to throw a punch every now and then.
显然我已经不能再扮演那样的角色了 但你可以
It's obvious, I can't play that role anymore but you can.
韦恩 我很开心大卫身边有你
Now, Wayne, I feel good knowing David's got you
我也要确保他能留住你 所以别担心
and I'm gonna make sure he keeps you. So save your breath,
我来搞定它 而你要保证你哥哥能再次当选
I'm gonna fix this and you are gonna make sure your brother gets re-elected.
好的
Fine.
但是 雪莉 不要忘了艾伦·米利肯有多危险
But, Sherry, don't you forget how dangerous Allan Milliken can be.
不会的
Oh, I won't forget.
我恐怕你忘了这点
I'm afraid you're the one who forgot
当你搞上他老婆的时候
when you decided to get involved with his wife.
一个多小时都没有杰克的消息了
No, we haven't heard directly from Jack in over an hour.
特种部队已在待命
But our delta teams are on stand by.
好的
I could.
你有尼娜·迈尔斯更多的资料吗?
Do you have any more information on Nina Meyers?
还没有
No, not yet.
金 我知道这对你很难
Look, Kim. I know it's hard but
但在事情结束之前 你要把个人感情放在一边
you're gonna have to try and put your feelings aside till all this is over.
我怎能把个人感情抛开?
How can I put my feelings aside?
我爸爸怎能把个人感情抛开?
How can my father put his feelings aside?
我花了三年时间才弄清楚那个女人
I spent the last three years of my life knowing that the woman
杀了我妈妈却被总统赦免了
who killed my mother was pardoned by the president.
她在外面
And that she's out there
逍遥法外
living her life.
这是不公平的
And it's wrong.
我知道
I know.
她愧对自己的赦免 不是吗? 她在买卖病毒
She's violating her pardon, isn't she? She's buying and selling a virus.
-金  -我们这次不能放过她
-Kim.  -We cannot let her get away this time.
我们不能意气用事
Look, let's not get ahead of ourselves, here.
拜托 托尼
Please, Tony.
她要为她做的一切付出代价
She has to pay for what she's done.
向我保证事情结束之后 你要让她受到惩罚
Promise me when this is all over you'll at least help make that happen.
-喂?  -托尼 我是克萝伊 金在吗?
-Yeah?  -Tony, this is Chloe. Is Kim in there?
-在  -我需要她
-Yeah.  -I need her.
好的 她来了
All right, she's on her way.
金!
Kim!
我会尽力而为
I'll do what I can.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘘 别吵
Shhh, it's ok.
乖孩子 漂亮又可爱
Good girl, nice and warm.
-什么事?  -克萝伊 萨拉扎的索引密码在哪里?
-Yes?  -Chloe, where are the index keys for Salazar?
-你是谁?  -1单元的Pat里克
-Who is this?  -Patrick in COM 1.
你们无权获取密码
You guys aren't authorize to access those keys.
我亲自去输密码
I'll come down and do it for you.
-我是想节省时间  -一分钟就下来
-I'm just trying to save some time.  -I'll be down in a minute.
好吧
Bye.
克萝伊 你找我吗?
Chloe. You wanted me?
米歇尔要我做局里人的简报
Michelle needs me to brief some people in division.
我还要去一单元给他们输索引密码
Then I have to go to COM 1 give them index keys.
我要你帮我照看些东西
I need you to watch some things up here for me.
你能在这儿替我一会儿吗?
Can you do your work from my station?
-我想可以  -很好
-Yeah, I guess so.  -Good.
这是安吉拉 她刚吃过东西准备睡觉 若她吵闹就把它塞到她嘴里
This is Angela. She's just been fed so she'll sleep. And if she gets fussy, just put that in her mouth.
但... 你不能把孩子带到这里来!
But... You can't have a baby in here!
卡佩勒 以为我把她给别人带了
Chapelle thinks I had someone pick her up so,
若他来了就把她藏起来
if he comes up, just keep her hidden.
好... 我... 但我不能...
Yeah... I... But I can't...
我十五分钟后回来
I'll be back in 15 minutes.
雷蒙!
Ramon!
杰克并非你所想象的那样
Jack's not who you think he is.
真的吗?
Is that right?
他为反恐局工作 他在陷害你
He's working with CTU. He's setting you up.
你以为我们兄弟会那样愚蠢吗?
You think that my brother and I are that stupid?
我们确定他是单独行动
We made sure that he's acting alone.
是你在想弄砸这次买卖吧
Don't you even think of undermining this deal.
杰克!
Hey, Jack!
我想是阿马多尔
I think it's Amador.
用免提 你说错一个字他就杀了你
Put this phone on speaker, you say one wrong word, and he will kill you.
明白吗?
You understand?
开始
Go.
喂
Hello.
东西在我这 准备好账号了吗?
I've got the product. Are you ready to show me your account?
是的
Yes.
我们说过可以查账的
We agreed you'd provide audit privileges.
是的 告诉我号码
Yes. Tell me your routing number.
77509210 账号是45508996.
77509210. Account number: 45508996.
收到
Ok.
资金在账户上吗? 准备好转帐了吗?
The funds are in their account? Ready to be transferred?
是的
Yeah.
波斯塔米塔东面有个旧矿山
There's an old mine east of Posta Mita.
一小时过十分钟后在最北端的建筑见
Meet me in the northern most building in an hour and ten minutes.
我带一个人保证安全 你也可以
I'll have one man with me for security. You may do the same.
很好
Good.
赫克托一回来我们就出发
We leave as soon as Hector arrives.
阿马多尔在行动
Amador's on the move.
-哪个方向?  -东
-What direction?  -East.
可能的目的地是哪儿?
Likely destination?
那方向有好几个村庄 任何一个都有可能
There's half a dozen villages along the vector. It could be anyone of them.
亚当是对的
With all due respect, Adam's right.
我们该让特种部队行动逮捕他
We should have ordered delta team to move in now and arrest Amador.
我已经说过了 如果阿马多尔没有带病毒 我们将失去它
We've been over this Gael. If the virus isn't under Amador's control, we could lose it.
我们要等杰克的确认
We've gotta wait for Jack's confirmation.
他怎样通知我们?
How will he let us know?
萨拉扎兄弟在监视他 他没法打电话
The Salazars are watching and it's not like he can make a phone call.
我不知道 他会找到办法
I don't know. He'll find a way.
大卫 你不认为我们应该通知墨西哥政府
David, don't you think it's about time we informed the Mexican government
我们所做的一切吗?
exactly what it is we're doing on their soil?
不 这样做会使行动受阻
No. I don't want to risk compromising the operation.
那么你该自己给总统打电话
Then you should call the president yourself.
一旦他知道这病毒的危害 就会理解了
Once he understands what kind of threat this virus poses he should ease off.
进来!
Yes!
先生 艾伦·米利肯在五号线等你
Sir, Allan Milliken is holding for you on line five.
谢谢 埃里克
Thank you, Eric.
喂 艾伦
Yes, Allan.
你他妈的以为自己在干什么?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
不要欺人太甚 大卫
Don't screw with me, David.
不是我挑起这场战争的
Hey, I didn't pick this fight.
你以为用你神经病的前妻制造的谣言就可以搞垮我?
You think you can enlist you psychopathic ex-wife to manufacture lies about me in order to bring me down?
没门
It's not going to happen.
你想让它结束?
You want it to stop?
那就别打我的法案和我弟弟的主意!
Keep your hands off my Health Care bill and stay away from my brother!
你说反了 你第弟该离我老婆远点
You've got it backwards. Your brother should have stayed away from my wife.
-得了吧 艾伦 都结束了  -真的吗?
-Come on, Allan, it's over.  -Really?
我正在看她和韦恩一个小时前在一起的照片
I'm looking at photographs of her and Wayne together an hour ago.
他只是想说服她和你讲讲道理
He was just trying to convince her to talk some sense into you.
我警告你 大卫 别把雪莉卷进来
I'm warning you, David. Pull Sherry off this.
否则你的法案就完了
Or the Health Care bill will be the least of your problems.
艾伦害怕了
Allan's scared.
艾伦在他害怕的时候是最危险的
Allan is at his most dangerous when he's scared.
告诉驻墨西哥大使 我要跟他们总统直接对话
Tell the Mexican ambassador that I'll be calling his president directly.
-她出去了  -我听到了 好吧 我又不是聋子
-She's out of town.  -I heard you the first time, sweetie, I'm not deaf.
我知道她在度假 我只想和她谈谈"懊丧的秋天"
I understand that she's on vacation. I just wanna talk to her about Chagrin Falls.
把这个号码给她 好吗?
And give her this number, ok?
-好的  -谢谢
-All right.  -Thank you.
大卫 什么事?
Yes, David?
我刚和艾伦·米利肯通过话
I just got off the phone with Allan Milliken.
这么快就有回应?
Well back up and quickly, huh?
-恩  -我想他应该非常生气吧
-Hmm-hmm  -I guess he was pretty upset.
你干了些什么?
What have you been up to?
按照你所说的去做啊
Exactly what you asked me to do.
我反击了
I'm fighting back.
"懊丧的秋天"是什么? 发生什么事了?
What's Chagrin Falls and what happened there?
是一些艾伦想隐瞒的一些事情
Well, it's something that Allan wants to keep buried.
我会告诉你一切 但不是现在
But, David, I'm gonna tell you everything but not just now.
如果要为你赢得这场战争 那我还有好多事情要做
I've got a lot to get done in a very short period of time if I'm gonna pull this off with you.
好吧
All right.
矿山的入口处有足够的地方隐藏你的人
Right here across from the opening of the mine. Looks like there's enough cover to hide your men.
很好
Right. Good.
-你找到埃德蒙兹了吗?  -没有 我说过 太黑了找不到
-Did you find Edmunds?  -No, I told you, it's too dark to find him.
那就不必找了
You don't need to look for Edmunds.
即使他联系了反恐局 他们也没有足够的时间赶来
Even if he contacted CTU they don't have enough time to get down here before the deal happens.
你为何如此肯定 他们现在不在那儿呢?
What makes you so sure they're not already here?
盖尔不是说过埃德蒙兹单干吗?
Didn't Gael tell you Edmunds came down alone?
为什么把她绑起来? 鲍尔说她会合作的
Why is she tied up? Bauer say he's going to buy her cooperation.
别担心 她知道该怎么做
Don't worry. She'll do what she's told.
拉姆 我能和你单独谈谈吗?
Ramon, can I speak to you in private?
什么事?
What is it?
计划不是这样的 我不喜欢
This is not the plan. I don't like it.
赫克托 我知道你为克劳迪娅事难过 不必为此恐慌
Hector, I know you're upset about Claudia. There's no reason to panick.
我不是恐慌 我很理智
I'm not panicking, I'm being sensible.
-这原本是你的主意  -而你曾经反对过 记得吗?
-This was your deal in the first place.  -And you were against it, remember?
我以前是错的 你是对的
You was right and I was wrong.
艾德蒙逃跑了 克劳迪娅死了 而这个女人又是被逼着干活
Edmund escapes, Claudia's dead and now this woman goes only along at gun point.
-感觉有问题  -我们没得选择
-It doesn't feel right.  -We don't have a choice.
卖家在等着交易 还不是因为你
The buyers are waiting for this deal to happen because of you.
-拉姆 事情没有按计划进行  -计划有变
-Ramon, things are not going as planned.  -The plans have changed.
反恐局 德斯勒
CTU, Dessler.
我们按照计划进行
We're following what you have started.
喂?
Hello?
拉姆 抱歉打扰一下 如果你还想交易的话我们必须走了
Ramon, sorry to interrupt. But if you want this deal to happen we've got to go now.
托尼! 杰克用手机打来了
Tony! Jack's on the line. He's using his cell as a one-way.
用扩音器
Put him on speaker.
阿马多尔一小时左右到波斯塔米塔矿山 我们到那差不多也要这么久
Amador's gonna be at the mine of Posta Mita in about an hour. Now, it's gonna take us that long to get there.
通知你的人就位
And get your men into position.
鲍尔是对的 我们要在阿马多尔之前到那
Bauer's right. Our men need to be in place before Amador gets there.
-我还没考虑好  -照我说的去做!
-I still haven't signed off on this.  -You do what I tell you to do!
通知你的人马 让他们到矿场外的村庄去
Now, call your men and tell them to be at the village, outside the mine.
该死 没电了 嘿 杰克 另外一个电话呢?
Dammit. No battery. Hey, Jack, where is the other phone?
在这儿
I've got it here.
断线了
It's disconnected.
他们已经告诉了我们要知道的情报
All right, they told us what we need to know.
通知特种部队就位
Get the delta teams in position.
设立隔离区 以防交易过程中病毒泄露
Make sure they set up a quarantine zone in case the virus gets out there in the exchange.
收到鲍尔来电 交易55分钟之后在波斯塔米塔的一个矿山进行
Bauer's been through. The deal is going down near a mine, just outside of Posta Mita in 55 minutes.
你们多久才能动身?
How long until you're able to mobilize?
我们已经确定坐标 已经行动了
We've got the coordinates. We're moving out now.
-你的人在行动  -他们会在攻击区三公里处埋伏
-Your men are mobilizing.  -They're bunking three kilometres from the strike zone.
你怎么确定交易地点?
How did you find out where the exchange was gonna be done?
鲍尔通知了反恐小组 55分钟后进行
Bauer got through to CTU. It's going down in 55 minutes.
你让你的人在三公里外待命? 这太远了吧
You're keeping your men three klicks away? That's not exactly a front row seat.
这样不会被发现
I'm keeping them out of site.
你怎么知道包裹里有病毒?
But how are you gonna confirm that the package contains the virus?
要派一个侦查员
I'm sending in a forward observer.
找到合适的人了吗?
Picked anyone yet?
还没
No, not yet.
我去
I'll do it.
我们有专门受过训练的人 埃德蒙兹
We've got people trained for that, Edmunds.
我也受训过
I'm trained for it, too.
而且我认得萨拉扎兄弟 记得吗?
Besides, I know the Salazars, remember?
你的手?
Your hand?
又不是战斗 侦察而已
This isn't combat. It's observation.
好吧
All right.
特雷! 给这个人侦察装备!
Trell! Get this man up with the surveillance package!
别说了 赫克托
Get over it, Hector.
除非你尊重我所说的话 到处都可能有埋伏
Not until you respect what I have to say. The Americans are behind it anyway.
-没时间争论了  -不要盛气凌人的和我说话
-There's no more time to argue.  -Stop talking down to me.
多亏了我 你才能站在这儿
Did you already forget the only reason why you are here is because of me?
-我把你弄出监狱  -鲍尔把我弄出来的 不是你
-I got you out of prison.  -Bauer got me out, not you.
我现在出来了 你就要像以前那样听命于我
And now that I'm out, you take orders from me just like you always have.
-拉姆...  -够了 赫克托! 别再说了
-Ramon...  -It's over, Hector! No more talking.
我们就要去交易了
We're gonna do the deal now.
鲍尔! 让她上车
Bauer! Get her in the car.
你不会得逞的 杰克
You can't control this, Jack.
上车
Just get in the car.
怎么回事呢? 求你别哭了 嘘 没事了
All right, what's the matter? Please don't cry. It's ok. Shh.
你干什么了?
What did you do to her?
-我什么也没做  -你肯定做什么了
-I didn't do anything to her.  -Well, you must have done something.
克萝伊 我保证我什么也没做
Chloe, look, I promise you, I didn't do anything to her.
我要整理我的档案了
Look, I'm gonna re-direct all my files back down to my desk.
-好  -还没完成
-Fine  -I didn't even finish with this.
杰克和尼娜 53分钟后在波斯塔米塔和阿马多尔会面
Jack and Nina are meeting Amador in 53 minutes in a place called Posta Mita.
特种部队情况怎么样?
What about delta force?
他们在周围三公里处设了防
They've established a preliminary three kilometer zone.
-那是什么?  -该死 我告诉过她的
-What the hell is that?  -Dammit I told her.
米歇尔 你去处理这事
Michelle. You take care of this, please.
-克萝伊 你出去  -我说过没人可照看她的
-That's it, Chloe. You're out of here.  -I told you I didn't have anyone to watch her.
你能照顾她了 我警告过你 你被停职了
You'll watch her. I gave you a warning, now you're suspended.
-那只是口头警告而已  -瑞恩
-It was a verbal warning only.  -Ryan
什么事?
What?
杰克和阿马多尔一小时内会面 但那地方卫星没有覆盖
Jack's meeting Amador in less than an hour but we have no visual satellite coverage of that area.
那和这孩子有什么关系?
What does that have to do with this baby?
我们不得不用电子加强过的音频监听 克萝伊是干这个的最佳人选
We're gonna have to use digitally enhanced audio coverage. Chloe is the best we have at that.
你是说我们得让这个女人在办公室里带孩子
So, you're telling me we have to let this woman raise her child
就因为没人可以顶替她的工作?
in our office because we don't have anyone who can do her job?
我的意思是 我们可以改天再讨论孩子问题
What I'm telling you is that maybe we should deal with Chloe's child care problems on another day.
我要干活了 谁来照看我的孩子?
I have work to do. Who's gonna look after my child?
-给金吧  -什么?
-Give her to Kim.  -What?
根据杰克提供给反恐局的情报 交易可能在此进行
Based on what CTU got from Jack, the meeting will probably take place here.
在镇上最北边的矿山上 我的位置在这里
By an old mine at the northern end of town. My position is gonna be here.
你要做的就是安排人到山后面
What I need from you is to put your men behind this ridge
直到确定病毒是真的
until we know that the virus is real.
很好的天然屏障
That's a good, natural cover. That'll work.
-你的人到那要多久?  -90秒
-How long will it take your men to get to the old mine?  -90 seconds.
-谢谢  -好运
-Thank you.  -Good luck.
其他人呢?
Where are the rest of the men?
-能找到的就这么多  -这不够!
-They were the only ones we could bring.  -It's not enough!
没关系 阿马多尔只带一个人
It's all right. Amador is only bringing one man.
那是他说的
Yeah, so he says.
你能不能别再自找麻烦?
Can you stop bringing problems where there are none?
我只是想确保我们的安全
I'm just trying to make sure we are covered.
你想要阻止交易 因为你没胆量了
No, you're trying to stop this deal from happening because you lost your nerve.
拉姆 事情变化太快了 我们根本没时间考虑
Ramon, things are moving too fast, we haven't had enough time to think them through.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
你说没事 不意味着就没事
Just because you say we'll be fine doesn't mean we'll be fine.
情况已经够糟了 别再添乱了 好吗?
The situation is difficult enough, don't make it worse! All right?
我不听呢?
Or what?
雷蒙!
Ramon!
如果你还想交易 我们必须要动身了
If you want this deal to happen we have to leave now.
我们要在阿马多尔之前20分钟到达那里
We have to be at the mine 20 minutes before Amador gets there...
交易取消了!
The deal is off!
赫克托 我们还没完呢
Hector, we're not done here.
该说的我已经说了
I've said what I need to say.
赫克托 仔细听我说
Listen to me, Hector, listen to me carefully.
如果我们不信守承诺 我们将不止损失钱财 还有信誉
If we don't give our buyers what we promised them we won't just lose money, we'll lose respect.
没了信誉 我们就一无所有
And without that, we have nothing.
我们还有命
We have our lives.
我们要走了
We're leaving now.
巴勃罗 费利佩 走!
Pablo Felipe vamos!
走!
Now!
赫克托 别这么做
Hector, don't do this.
赫克托.
Hector
赫克托!
Hector!